<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metapackage xmlns:os="http://opensuse.org/Standards/One_Click_Install" xmlns="http://opensuse.org/Standards/One_Click_Install">
  <group distversion="openSUSE Main Repository">
    <repositories>
      <repository recommended="true" format="yast">
        <name>Main Repository (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ar">المستودع الرئيسي (حرة)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ast">Repositoriu principal (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ca">Repositori principal (Programari de codi obert)</name>
        <name xml:lang="cs">Hlavní repozitář (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="da">Hovedsoftwarekilde (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="de">Haupt-Repository (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="el">Κύριο Αποθετήριο (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="es">Repositorio principal (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="et">Üldine hoidla (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="fa">مخازن اصلی (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="fi">Pääasennuslähde (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="fr">Dépôt principal (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="gl">Repositorio Principal (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="hr">Glavni repozitorij (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="hu">Fő telepítési forrás (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="id">Repositori Utama (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="it">Repository principale (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ja">メインリポジトリ (オープンソース)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ka">Main Repository (ღია პროგრამები)</name>
        <name xml:lang="km">ឃ្លាំង​ចម្បង (កម្មវិធី​កូដ​ចំហ)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ko">주 저장소 (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="lt">Pagrindinė saugykla su AKPĮ (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="nb">Hovedpakkebrønn (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="nl">Hoofd-opslagruimte (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="pa">ਮੁੱਖ ਰਿਪੋਜ਼ਟਰੀ (ਓਪਨ-ਸੋਰਸ)</name>
        <name xml:lang="pl">Repozytorium główne (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="pt">Repositório Principal (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Repositório principal (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ro">Sursă de instalare principală (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ru">Основной репозиторий (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="sk">Hlavný repozitár (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="sv">Huvudförrådet (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="th">คลังแพกเกจหลัก (ซอฟต์แวร์เสรี)</name>
        <name xml:lang="tr">Ana Depo (AKY)</name>
        <name xml:lang="uk">Головне сховище (ВПЗ)</name>
        <name xml:lang="wa">Mwaisse depot (OSS)</name>
        <name xml:lang="zh_CN">主软件源（开源软件）</name>
        <name xml:lang="zh_TW">主要套件庫 (OSS)</name>
        <summary>Main repository of openSUSE Tumbleweed including only Open Source Software</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ar">المستودع الرئيسي لأوبن سوزي  Tumbleweed مع البرمجيات مفتوحة المصدر فقط</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ca">Repositori principal d'openSUSE Tumbleweed que inclou només programari de codi obert</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="cs">Hlavní repozitář openSUSE Tumbleweed obsahující pouze software s otevřeným kódem</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="da">Hovedsoftwarekilden for openSUSE Tumbleweed, som kun inkluderer open source software</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="de">Hauptrepository von openSUSE Tumbleweed welches ausschließlich Open Source Software beinhaltet</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="el">Κύριο αποθετήριο του openSUSE Tumbleweed που συμπεριλαμβάνει μόνο Λογισμικό Ανοικτού Κώδικα</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="es">Repositorio principal de openSUSE Tumbleweed incluyendo solo software de código abierto</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="et">Peahoidla OpenSUSE Tumbleweedi ainult avatud lähtekoodiga tarkvarale OSS</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="fa">مخازن اصلی openSUSE Tumbleweed شامل فقط نرم افزارهای متن باز</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="fi">openSUSE Tumbleweed -perusasennuslähde sisältää vain avoimen lähdekoodin ohjelmia</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="fr">Dépôt principal d'openSUSE Tumbleweed contenant seulement les logiciels Open Source</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="gl">Repositorio principal de openSUSE Tumbleweed que inclúe só software de código aberto</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="id">Repositori utama openSUSE Tumbleweed yang hanya berisi Perangkat Lunak Sumber Terbuka</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="it">Repository principale di openSUSE Tumbleweed che include solo programmi Open Source</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ja">オープンソースソフトウエアだけを含む、 openSUSE Tumbleweed のメインリポジトリ</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="lt">openSUSE Tumbleweed pagrindinė saugykla, turinti tik atviro kodo programinę įrangą</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="nb">Hovedpakkebrønn for openSUSE Tumbleweed som kun inneholder programvare med åpen kildekode</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="nl">Hoofd-opslagruimte van openSUSE Tumbleweed met alleen opensource-software</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="pl">Główne repozytorium openSUSE Tumbleweed zawierające tylko oprogramowanie Open Source</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Repositório principal do openSUSE Tumbleweed contendo somente software de código aberto</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ru">Основной репозиторий openSUSE Tumbleweed, включающий только программное обеспечение с открытым кодом</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="sk">Hlavný repozitár openSUSE Tumbleweed, ktorý obsahuje iba Open Source Software</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="sv">Huvudförrådet för openSUSE Tumbleweed , innehåller enbart open source-mjukvara</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="uk">Головне сховище openSUSE Tumbleweed, яке містить лише ПЗ з відкритим кодом</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">openSUSE Tumbleweed 主软件源，仅包含开源软件</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">openSUSE Tumbleweed 的主要套件庫，僅包含開放原碼的軟體</summary>
        <description>The big Open Source Software (OSS) repository for openSUSE, giving you access to thousands of packages maintained by the openSUSE team. (Due to the size of the repository, adding it may take some time. 512 MB of RAM or an enabled SWAP partition are highly recommended in case you want to access this repository at installation time.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="ar">مستودع البرمجيات الحرة (OSS) الكبرى لاوبن سوزي تتيح الوصول إلى آلاف الحزم التي يحتفظ بها فريق اوبن سوزي. (نظرا لحجم المستودع ، فإن إضافته تستغرق بعض الوقت  ويستهلك 512 ميغابايت من ذاكرة الوصول العشوائي او من قسم SWAP نوصى بشده بالوصول لهذا المستودع اثناء وقت التنصيب.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="ca">El gran repositori de programari de codi obert (Open Source Software (OSS)) per a l'openSUSE, que us dona accés a milers de paquets mantinguts per l'equip d'openSUSE. (A causa de la mida del repositori, afegir-lo pot trigar força estona. És molt recomanable tenir un mínim de 512 MB de RAM o una partició d'intercanvi activa en cas que hi vulgueu accedir durant la instal·lació.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="cs">Velký repozitář se softwarem s otevřeným kódem pro openSUSE Factory vám dává přístup k tisícům balíčků spravovaných týmem openSUSE. (Vzhledem k velikosti tohoto repozitáře může jeho přidání vyžadovat delší čas. Pokud k repozitáři chcete přistupovat během instalace, doporučujeme minimálně 512 MB RAM nebo aktivní odkládací oddíl.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="da">Den store open source softwarekilde (OSS) til openSUSE, som giver dig adgang til tusindvis af pakker, vedligeholdt af openSUSE-holdet. (På grund af størrelsen på softwarekilden kan tilføjelse af den tage noget tid. 512 MB RAM eller en aktiveret SWAP-partition anbefales, hvis du vil have adgang til denne softwarekilde under installation.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="de">Das große  'Open Source Software' (OSS) Repository für openSUSE, das Ihnen Zugriff auf tausende vom openSUSE-Team gepflegte Pakete gibt. (Aufgrund der Größe des Repositorys kann das Hinzufügen einige Zeit in Anspruch nehmen. Mindestens 512MB RAM oder eine aktivierte SWAP-Partition werden dringend empfohlen, falls Sie während der Installation dieses Repository verwenden wollen.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="el">Το μεγάλο αποθετήριο Λογισμικού Ανοικτού Κώδικα (ΛΑΚ) για openSUSE, που σας δίνει πρόσβαση σε χιλιάδες πακέτα που συντηρούνται από την ομάδα openSUSE. (Λόγω του μεγάλου μεγέθους του αποθετηρίου, η προσθήκη του θα πάρει ώρα. Συνίσταται 512MB RAM ή ενεργοποίηση της κατάτμησης SWAP σε περίπτωση που θέλετε να προσθέσετε αυτό το αποθετήριο κατά την εγκατάσταση.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="es">El gran repositorio de software de código abierto (OSS) de openSUSE le da acceso a miles de paquetes mantenidos por el equipo de openSUSE. (Debido al tamaño del repositorio, el añadirlo puede llevar algún tiempo. 512 MB de memoria RAM o habilitar una partición SWAP es altamente recomendable en caso que desee acceder a este repositorio en el momento de la instalación)</description>
        <description xml:lang="et">OpenSUSE suur avatud lähtekoodiga tarkvara (OSS) hoidla, mis annab teile juurdepääsu tuhandetele OpenSUSE meeskonna hallatavatele pakettidele. (Repositooriumi suuruse tõttu võib selle lisamine võtta natuke aega. 512 MB RAM-i või lubatud SWAP-sektsiooni on soovitatav kasutada juhul, kui soovite sellele hoidlale juurde pääseda paigaldamise ajal.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="fa">مخزن بزرگ نرم افزارهای متن باز (OSS) برای openSUSE ، به شما دسترسی به هزاران بسته که توسط تیم openSUSE نگه داری میشود را میدهد. ( به دلیل اندازه ی مخزن، اضافه کردن آن ممکن است کمی زمان ببرد.اگر میخواهید در زمان نصب از این مخازن استفاده کنید، میزان  حافظه ی 512 مگابایت رم و یا پارتیشن فعال SWAP به شدت توصیه میشود.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="fi">Suuri avoimen lähdekoodin ohjelmistoasennuslähde (OSS) openSUSElle. Täältä löydät tuhansia openSUSE-tiimin ylläpitämiä paketteja. (Asennuslähteen koon vuoksi lisääminen saattaa viedä aikaa. 512 Mt keskusmuistia tai käyttöön otettu SWAP-osio ovat erittäin suositeltavia, jos haluat ottaa tämän asennuslähteen käyttöön asennuksen aikana.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="fr">Le principal dépôt de logiciels Open Source (OSS) pour openSUSE , vous donne accès à des milliers de paquets maintenus par l'équipe d'openSUSE. (En raison de la taille du dépôt, l'ajouter peut prendre du temps. 512 Mo de RAM ou une partition SWAP active sont fortement recommandés si vous voulez y accéder au moment de l'installation.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="gl">O gran repositorio de Software de código aberto (OSS) para openSUSE , dálle acceso a milleiros de paquetes mantidos polo equipo de openSUSE. (Debido ao tamaño do repositorio, engadilo podería levar algún tempo. É moi recomendábel ter 512 MB de RAM ou ter activada a partición de intercambio ou SWAP se desexa acceder a este repositorio á hora de instalar.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="id">Repositori Perangkat Lunak Sumber Terbuka (OSS) besar untuk openSUSE, memberikan Anda akses ke ribuan paket yang dikelola oleh tim openSUSE. (Karena ukuran dari repositori, menambahkannya mungkin memerlukan waktu beberapa saat. 512 MB RAM atau partisi SWAP yang diaktifkan sangat dianjurkan jika Anda ingin mengakses repositori ini pada saat instalasi.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="it">Il grande repository di programmi Open Source (OSS) di openSUSE, che fornisce l'accesso a migliaia di pacchetti mantenuti dal team openSUSE. A causa delle dimensioni del repository, la sua aggiunta potrebbe richiedere un po' di tempo. Si consiglia fortemente di utilizzare un sistema con almeno 512MB di RAM o con una partizione di SWAP attiva, qualora si desideri avere accesso a questo repository durante l'installazione.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ja">openSUSE 向けの巨大なオープンソース・ソフトウエアリポジトリです。 openSUSE チームによって管理されている、何千ものパッケージにアクセスすることができます。 (リポジトリのサイズが巨大であるため、このリポジトリを追加するにはしばらくの時間がかかります。また、インストールの際にリポジトリにアクセスする場合、512 MB の RAM とスワップの利用を強くお勧めします。)</description>
        <description xml:lang="lt">Didelė atviro kodo programinės įrangos openSUSE saugykla, leidžianti parsisiųsti tūkstančius openSUSE komandos prižiūrimų paketų. (Dėl saugyklos didumo, jos pridėjimas gali užtrukti. Jei norite šią saugyklą pasiekti diegimo metu, patariame turėti bent 512 MB RAM arba įgalintą mainų (SWAP) skaidinį.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="nb">Den store pakkebrønnen for åpen kildekode (OSS) for openSUSE gir deg tilgang til tusenvis av pakker som vedlikeholdes av openSUSE-gruppen. (På grunn av størrelsen kan det ta en stund å legge til pakkebrønnen (512 MB RAM eller en aktivert vekselsminnepartisjon anbefales sterkt hvis du ønsker tilgang til denne pakkebrønnen under installasjonen.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="nl">De grote opensource-software (OSS) opslagruimte van openSUSE geeft u toegang tot duizenden pakketten die door het openSUSE-team worden onderhouden. (Vanwege de grootte van deze bron kan het toevoegen ervan enige tijd in beslag nemen. Minimaal 512 MB RAM of een geactiveerde partitie met wisselgeheugen (swap) is ten zeerste aanbevolen als u deze bron tijdens de installatie wilt gebruiken.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="pl">Wielkie repozytorium oprogramowania Open Source (OSS) dla openSUSE, które zawiera tysiące pakietów utrzymywanych przez zespół openSUSE. (Z racji rozmiarów dodanie tego repozytorium może zająć trochę czasu. Jeśli to repozytorium ma być użyte podczas instalacji, zalecane jest posiadanie 512MB pamięci RAM lub aktywnej partycji wymiany.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="pt_BR">O grande repositório de software de código aberto (OSS) para o openSUSE Factory, fornecendo-lhe acesso a milhares de pacotes mantidos pela equipe do openSUSE. (Devido ao tamanho do repositório, sua inclusão pode demorar algum tempo. É altamente recomendado possuir 512MB de RAM ou uma partição de troca ativada caso você deseje acessar este repositório durante a instalação.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="ru">Большой репозиторий программного обеспечения с открытым кодом (OSS) для openSUSE 13.2, дающий вам доступ к тысячам пакетов, поддерживаемых командой openSUSE. (Из-за размера репозитория его добавление может занять некоторое время. Если вы хотите получить доступ к этому репозиторию во время установки, очень рекомендуется 512 МБ RAM или включённый раздел подкачки.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="sk">Veľký repozitár Open Source Software (OSS) pre openSUSE, ktorý vám dáva prístup k tisícom balíkom, ktoré sú udržované tímom openSUSE. (Ak chcete mať prístup k tomuto repozitáru počas inštalácie, doporučujeme mať 512 MB RAM alebo povolený odkladací diskový oddiel SWAP kvôli veľkosti repozitára. Jeho pridanie môže trvať istý čas.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="sv">Det stora Open Source Software (OSS) förrådet för openSUSE som ger dig åtkomst till tusentals paket underhållna av openSUSE teamet. (På grund av dess storlek kan det ta ett tag att lägga till förrådet. 512 MB RAM eller en SWAP-partition är mycket rekommenderat om du vill ha tillgång till detta förråd under installationen.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="uk">Це велике сховище програмного забезпечення з відкритим кодом (ВПЗ) для openSUSE, яке надає вам доступ до тисяч пакунків, які підтримуються командою openSUSE. (Через те, що сховище має величезний розмір, його додавання може тривати довго. Рекомендовано мати 512 МБ операційної пам'яті або розділ свопінгу, якщо ви хочете мати доступ до сховища під час встановлення системи.)</description>
        <description xml:lang="zh_CN">庞大的 openSUSE 开源软件源，提供由 openSUSE 团队维护的数千个软件包。（由于软件源容量太大，添加它可能要花费点时间。若想要在系统安装时访问该源，强烈建议有 512MB 内存或启用硬盘交换分区。）</description>
        <description xml:lang="zh_TW">openSUSE 巨大的開放原始碼軟體 (OSS) 套件庫，提供了數千個由 openSUSE 團隊維護的套件讓您取用。(由於這個套件庫非常大，要加入它會花上一些時間。如果您要在安裝時存取此套件庫，強烈建議至少 512 MB 的記憶體或可用的 SWAP 分割區。)</description>
        <url>http://download.opensuse.org/ports/ppc/tumbleweed/repo/oss/</url>
      </repository>
      <repository recommended="false" format="yast">
        <name>Main Repository (Sources)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ar">المستودع الرئيسي (المصادر)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ast">Repositoriu principal (Fontes)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ca">Repositori principal (Fonts)</name>
        <name xml:lang="cs">Hlavní repozitář (zdroje)</name>
        <name xml:lang="da">Hovedsoftwarekilde (kildekoder)</name>
        <name xml:lang="de">Haupt-Repository (Quellen)</name>
        <name xml:lang="el">Κύριο Αποθετήριο (Πηγές)</name>
        <name xml:lang="es">Repositorio principal (fuentes)</name>
        <name xml:lang="et">Üldine hoidla (lähtekoodid)</name>
        <name xml:lang="fa">مخازن اصلی (منابع)</name>
        <name xml:lang="fi">Pääasennuslähde (lähdekoodit)</name>
        <name xml:lang="fr">Dépôt principal (Sources)</name>
        <name xml:lang="gl">Repositorio principal (Fontes)</name>
        <name xml:lang="hr">Glavni repozitorij (programski kod)</name>
        <name xml:lang="hu">Elsődleges telepítési forrás (források)</name>
        <name xml:lang="id">Repositori Utama (Sumber)</name>
        <name xml:lang="it">Repository principale (Sorgenti)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ja">メインリポジトリ (ソース)</name>
        <name xml:lang="km">ឃ្លាំង​ចម្បង (ប្រភព)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ko">주 저장소 (소스)</name>
        <name xml:lang="lt">Pagrindinė saugykla (šaltiniai)</name>
        <name xml:lang="nb">Hovedpakkebrønn (kildekode)</name>
        <name xml:lang="nl">Hoofd-opslagruimte (broncode)</name>
        <name xml:lang="pa">ਮੁੱਖ ਰਿਪੋਜ਼ਟਰੀ (ਸਰੋਤ)</name>
        <name xml:lang="pl">Repozytorium główne (pakiety źródłowe)</name>
        <name xml:lang="pt">Repositório Principal (Fontes)</name>
        <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Repositório principal (fontes)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ro">Sursă de instalare principală (cod sursă)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ru">Основной репозиторий (Исходные коды)</name>
        <name xml:lang="sk">Hlavný repozitár (Zdrojové kódy)</name>
        <name xml:lang="sv">Huvudförråd (källkod)</name>
        <name xml:lang="th">คลังแพกเกจหลัก (ต้นฉบับ)</name>
        <name xml:lang="tr">Ana Depo (Kaynaklar)</name>
        <name xml:lang="uk">Головне сховище (джерела)</name>
        <name xml:lang="wa">Mwaisse depot (Sourdants)</name>
        <name xml:lang="zh_CN">主软件源（源代码）</name>
        <name xml:lang="zh_TW">主要套件庫 (原始碼)</name>
        <summary>Main repository of openSUSE Tumbleweed (Source packages)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ar">مستودع أوبن سوزي Tumbleweed الرئيسي (حزم المصدر)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ca">Repositori principal d'openSUSE Tumbleweed (Paquets de codi font)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="cs">Hlavní repozitář openSUSE Tumbleweed (zdrojové balíčky)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="da">Hovedsoftwarekilden for openSUSE Tumbleweed (kildekode-pakker)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="de">Hauptverzeichnis von openSUSE Tumbleweed ( Quellpakete )</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="el">Κύριο Αποθετήριο του openSUSE Tumbleweed (Πηγαία Πακέτα)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="es">Repositorio principal de openSUSE Tumbleweed (código fuente)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="et">OpenSUSE Tumbleweed peahoidla (lähtekoodipaketid)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="fa">مخازن اصلی openSUSE Tumbleweed (بسته های source)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="fi">openSUSE Tumbleweed -jakelun perusasennuslähde (lähdekoodipaketit)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="fr">Dépôt principal d'openSUSE Tumbleweed (Paquets Sources)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="gl">Repositorio principal de openSUSE Tumbleweed (Paquetes de fontes)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="id">Repositori utama openSUSE Tumbleweed (Paket-paket Sumber)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="it">Repository principale di openSUSE Tumbleweed (Pacchetti sorgente)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ja">openSUSE Tumbleweed のメインリポジトリ (ソースパッケージ)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="lt">openSUSE Tumbleweed pagrindinė saugykla (šaltinių paketai)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="nb">Hovedpakkebrønn for openSUSE Tumbleweed (kildekodepakker)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="nl">Hoofd-opslagruimte van openSUSE Tumbleweed (broncodepakketten)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="pl">Główne repozytorium openSUSE Tumbleweed (Pakiety źródłowe)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Repositório principal do openSUSE Tumbleweed (pacotes fonte)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ru">Основной репозиторий openSUSE Tumbleweed (Пакеты с исходным кодом)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="sk">Hlavný repozitár openSUSE Tumbleweed (Zdrojové balíky)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="sv">Huvudförråd för openSUSE Tumbleweed (källkodspaket)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="uk">Головне сховище для openSUSE Tumbleweed (джерельні пакунки)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">openSUSE Tumbleweed 主软件源（源代码）</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">openSUSE Tumbleweed 的主要套件庫(原始碼套件)</summary>
        <description>The repository of all source packages in openSUSE Tumbleweed. For experts only.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ar">مستودع جميع حزم المصدر في أوبن سوزي Tumbleweed. للخبراء فقط.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ca">El repositori de tots els paquets de codi font a l'openSUSE Tumbleweed. Només per a experts.</description>
        <description xml:lang="cs">Repozitář všech zdrojových balíčků z openSUSE Tumbleweedu. Pouze pro zkušené uživatele.</description>
        <description xml:lang="da">Softwarekilden for alle kildekode-pakker i openSUSE Tumbleweed. Kun for eksperter.</description>
        <description xml:lang="de">Das Repository aller Quelltext-Pakete in openSUSE Tumbleweed. Nur für Experten.</description>
        <description xml:lang="el">Το αποθετήριο για όλα τα πηγαιά πακέτα στο openSUSE Tumbleweed. Μόνο για προχωρημένους.</description>
        <description xml:lang="es">El repositorio de todo el código fuente en openSUSE Tumbleweed. Solo para expertos.</description>
        <description xml:lang="et">Kõigi lähtekoodipakettide hoidla OpenSUSE Tumbleweedis. Ainult ekspertidele.</description>
        <description xml:lang="fa">مخازن شامل تمامی بسته های منبع  کد برای openSUSE Tumbleweed. فقط برای افراد متخصص است.</description>
        <description xml:lang="fi">Asennuslähde kaikille openSUSE Tumbleweed -jakelun lähdekoodipaketeille. Vain asiantuntijoille.</description>
        <description xml:lang="fr">Le dépôt de tous les paquets source d'openSUSE Tumbleweed. Pour experts seulement.</description>
        <description xml:lang="gl">O repositorio de todos os paquetes de fontes de openSUSE Tumbleweed. Só para expertos.</description>
        <description xml:lang="id">Repositori dari semua paket sumber di openSUSE Tumbleweed. Untuk pengguna ahli saja.</description>
        <description xml:lang="it">Il repository di tutti i pacchetti dei sorgenti di openSUSE Tumbleweed. Solo per esperti.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ja">openSUSE Tumbleweed の全てのソースパッケージを含むリポジトリ。熟練者向けです。</description>
        <description xml:lang="lt">Visų openSUSE Tumbleweed šaltinių paketų saugykla. Tik ekspertams.</description>
        <description xml:lang="nb">Pakkebrønn for alle kildekodepakker for openSUSE Tumbleweed. Bare for avanserte brukere.</description>
        <description xml:lang="nl">De opslagruimte van alle broncodepakketten voor openSUSE Tumbleweed. Alleen voor ervaren gebruikers.</description>
        <description xml:lang="pl">Repozytorium zawiera wszystkie pakiety źródłowe systemu openSUSE Tumbleweed. Tylko dla ekspertów.</description>
        <description xml:lang="pt_BR">Repositório de todos os pacotes fonte no openSUSE Tumbleweed. Somente para usuários avançados.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ru">Репозиторий со всеми пакетами с исходным кодом в openSUSE Tumbleweed. Только для экспертов.</description>
        <description xml:lang="sk">Repozitár všetkých zdrojových balíkov v openSUSE Tumbleweed. Iba pre expertov.</description>
        <description xml:lang="sv">Förrådet med alla källkodspaket i openSUSE Tumbleweed. För experter.</description>
        <description xml:lang="uk">Сховище для всіх джерельних пакунків у openSUSE Tumbleweed. Тільки для знавців.</description>
        <description xml:lang="zh_CN">openSUSE Tumbleweed 全部源代码包的软件源。仅供专家使用。</description>
        <description xml:lang="zh_TW">openSUSE Tumbleweed 所有原始碼套件的套件庫。僅提供專家使用。</description>
        <url>http://download.opensuse.org/ports/ppc/source/tumbleweed/repo/oss/</url>
      </repository>
      <repository recommended="false" format="yast">
        <name>Main Repository (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ar">المستودع الرئيسي (التصحيح)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ast">Repositoriu principal (DEPURACIÓN)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ca">Repositori principal (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="cs">Hlavní repozitář (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="da">Hovedsoftwarekilde (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="de">Haupt-Repository (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="el">Κύριο Αποθετήριο (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="es">Repositorio principal (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="et">Peahoidla (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="fa">مخازن اصلی (اشکال زدایی)</name>
        <name xml:lang="fi">Pääasennuslähde (Debug)</name>
        <name xml:lang="fr">Dépôt principal (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="gl">Repositorio Principal (DEPURACIÓN)</name>
        <name xml:lang="hr">Glavni repozitorij (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="hu">Elsődleges telepítési forrás (debug)</name>
        <name xml:lang="id">Repositori Utama (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="it">Repository principale (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ja">メインリポジトリ (デバッグ)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ka">Main Repository (გამართვის პაკეტები)</name>
        <name xml:lang="km">ឃ្លាំង​ចម្បង (បំបាត់​កំហុស)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ko">주 저장소 (디버그)</name>
        <name xml:lang="lt">Pagrindinė saugykla (Derinimui)</name>
        <name xml:lang="nb">Hovedpakkebrønn (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="nl">Hoofd-opslagruimte (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="pa">ਮੁੱਖ ਰਿਪੋਜ਼ਟਰੀ (ਡੀਬੱਗ)</name>
        <name xml:lang="pl">Repozytorium główne (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="pt">Repositório Principal (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Repositório principal (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ro">Sursă de instalare principală (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="ru">Основной репозиторий (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="sk">Hlavný repozitár (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="sv">Huvudförrådet (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="th">คลังแพกเกจหลัก (แพกเกจดีบั๊ก)</name>
        <name xml:lang="tr">Ana Depo (HATA AYIKLAMA)</name>
        <name xml:lang="uk">Головне сховище (DEBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="wa">Mwaisse depot (DISBUG)</name>
        <name xml:lang="zh_CN">主调试源</name>
        <name xml:lang="zh_TW">主要套件庫 (偵錯)</name>
        <summary>Main repository of openSUSE Tumbleweed including the debuginfo packages</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ar">المستودع الرئيسي للأوبن سوزي Tumbleweed بما في ذلك حزم debuginfo</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ca">Repositori principal d'openSUSE Tumbleweed que inclou els paquets d'informació de depuració</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="cs">Hlavní repozitář openSUSE Tumbleweed obsahující balíčky debuginfo</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="da">Hovedsoftwarekilde for openSUSE Tumbleweed som inkluderer debuginfo-pakker</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="de">Hauptverzeichnis von openSUSE Tumbleweed einschließlich der debuginfo Pakete</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="el">Κύριο αποθετριο του openSUSE Tumbleweed συμπεριλαμβανομένων και των πακέτων debuginfo</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="es">Repositorio principal de openSUSE Tumbleweed incluyendo los paquetes de depuración</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="et">OpenSUSE Tumbleweedi peahoidla koos silumisinfo pakettidega</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="fa">مخازن اصلی openSUSE Tumbleweed شامل بسته های debuginfo</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="fi">OpenSUSE Tumbleweedin pääasennuslähde, joka sisältää debuginfo-paketit</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="fr">Dépôt principal d'openSUSE Tumbleweed contenant les paquets debuginfo</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="gl">Repositorio principal de openSUSE Tumbleweed que inclúe paquetes de información de depuración (debuginfo)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="id">Repositori utama openSUSE Tumbleweed yang berisi paket-paket debuginfo</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="it">Repository principale di openSUSE Tumbleweed che include i pacchetti debuginfo</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ja">デバッグ情報パッケージを含む openSUSE Tumbleweed のメインリポジトリ</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="lt">openSUSE Tumbleweed pagrindinė saugykla, turinti derinimo informacijos paketus</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="nb">Hovedpakkebrønn for openSUSE Tumbleweed som inneholder pakker med feilsøkingsinformasjon</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="nl">Hoofd-opslagruimte van openSUSE Tumbleweed, met debuginfo-pakketten</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="pl">Główne repozytorium openSUSE Tumbleweed zawierające pakiety debuginfo</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Repositório principal do openSUSE Tumbleweed contendo os pacotes debuginfo</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ru">Основной репозиторий openSUSE Tumbleweed, включающий пакеты debuginfo</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="sk">Hlavný repozitár pre openSUSE Tumbleweed, ktorý obsahuje balíky s ladiacimi informáciami (debuginfo)</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="sv">Huvudförrådet för openSUSE Tumbleweed innehåller debuginfo-paketen</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="uk">Головне сховище openSUSE Tumbleweed, яке містить пакунки debuginfo</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">openSUSE Tumbleweed 主软件源包含调试信息包</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">openSUSE Tumbleweed 的主要套件庫，包含偵錯套件</summary>
        <description>This repository is useful for those that want to debug applications on openSUSE Tumbleweed. For experts only.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ar">هذا المستودع مفيد لمن يرغب في تصحيح التطبيقات على أوبن سوزي Tumbleweed. للخبراء فقط.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ca">Aquest repositori és útil per a qui vulgui depurar aplicacions a l'openSUSE Tumbleweed. Només per a experts.</description>
        <description xml:lang="cs">Tento repozitář je užitečný pro všechny, kdo chtějí ladit aplikace pro openSUSE Tumbleweed. Určeno pouze pro experty.</description>
        <description xml:lang="da">Denne softwarekilde er nyttig for dem, der ønsker at fejlsøge programmer på openSUSE Tumbleweed. Kun for eksperter.</description>
        <description xml:lang="de">Diese Softwarequelle ist für diejenigen nützlich, die Anwendungen auf openSUSE Tumbleweed debuggen wollen. Nur für Experten.</description>
        <description xml:lang="el">Αυτό το αποθετήριο είναι χρήσιμο για όσους θέλουν να αποσφαλματώσουν εφαρμογές στο openSUSE Tumbleweed. Μόνο για προχωρημένους.</description>
        <description xml:lang="es">Este repositorio es útil para aquellos que quieren depurar aplicaciones en openSUSE Tumbleweed. Solo para expertos.</description>
        <description xml:lang="et">See hoidla on kasulik neile, kes soovivad siluda rakendusi openSUSE Tumbleweedis. Ainult ekspertidele.</description>
        <description xml:lang="fa">این مخزن برای آنهایی که میخواهند نرم افزارها را در openSUSE Tumbleweed اشکال زدایی کنند مناسب است. فقط برای افراد متخصص است.</description>
        <description xml:lang="fi">Tämä asennuslähde on tarpeen niille, jotka haluavat paikantaa vikoja openSUSE Tumbleweedin sovelluksista. Vain asiantuntijoille.</description>
        <description xml:lang="fr">Ce dépôt est utile pour ceux qui souhaitent déboguer des applications sous openSUSE Tumbleweed. Pour experts seulement.</description>
        <description xml:lang="gl">Este repositorio é útil para aqueles que desexan depurar aplicativos de openSUSE Tumbleweed. Só para expertos.</description>
        <description xml:lang="id">Repositori ini berguna bagi mereka yang ingin melakukan debug terhadap aplikasi pada openSUSE Tumbleweed. Untuk pengguna ahli saja.</description>
        <description xml:lang="it">Questo repository è utile per coloro che desiderano effettuare il debug delle applicazioni su openSUSE Tumbleweed. Solo per esperti.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ja">このリポジトリは、 openSUSE Tumbleweed のアプリケーションをデバッグする際に便利なリポジトリです。熟練者向けです。</description>
        <description xml:lang="lt">Ši saugykla naudinga tiems, kas nori derinti programas su openSUSE Tumbleweed. Tik ekspertams.</description>
        <description xml:lang="nb">Denne pakkebrønnen er nyttig hvis du vil feilsøke programmer i openSUSE Tumbleweed. Kun for avanserte brukere.</description>
        <description xml:lang="nl">Deze bron is bedoeld voor diegenen die fouten in programma's in openSUSE Tumbleweed willen opsporen. Alleen voor ervaren gebruikers.</description>
        <description xml:lang="pl">Repozytorium dla tych, którzy pragną debugować programy w openSUSE Tumbleweed. Tylko dla zaawansowanych.</description>
        <description xml:lang="pt_BR">Este repositório é útil para aqueles que desejam depurar aplicações no openSUSE Tumbleweed. Somente para usuários avançados.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ru">Этот репозиторий полезен для тех, кто хочет отлаживать приложения на openSUSE Tumbleweed. Только для экспертов.</description>
        <description xml:lang="sk">Tento repozitár je užitočný pre tých, ktorí chcú ladiť programy na openSUSE Tumbleweed. Len pre expertov.</description>
        <description xml:lang="sv">Detta förråd är användbart för dem som vill avlusa program i openSUSE Tumbleweed. Enbart för experter.</description>
        <description xml:lang="uk">Це сховище придатне для тих, хто хоче зневаджувати програми на openSUSE Tumbleweed. Тільки для знавців.</description>
        <description xml:lang="zh_CN">本软件源只对那些想要在 openSUSE Tumbleweed 中调试程序的人有用。仅供专家使用。</description>
        <description xml:lang="zh_TW">這個套件庫對想要在 openSUSE Tumbleweed 偵錯應用程式非常有用。僅提供專家使用。</description>
        <url>http://download.opensuse.org/ports/ppc/debug/tumbleweed/repo/oss/</url>
      </repository>
      <repository recommended="true" format="rpm-md">
        <name>Main Update Repository</name>
        <name xml:lang="ar">مستودع التحديث الرئيسي</name>
        <name xml:lang="ast">Repositoriu principal d'anovamientu</name>
        <name xml:lang="ca">Repositori d'actualització principal</name>
        <name xml:lang="cs">Hlavní aktualizační repozitář</name>
        <name xml:lang="da">Hovedopdateringskilden</name>
        <name xml:lang="de">Hauptaktualisierungs-Repository</name>
        <name xml:lang="el">Κύριο Αποθετήριο Ενημερώσεων</name>
        <name xml:lang="es">Repositorio principal de actualizaciones</name>
        <name xml:lang="et">Peahoidla uuendustele</name>
        <name xml:lang="fa">مخازن اصلی به روز رسانی</name>
        <name xml:lang="fi">Perusasennuslähde päivityksille</name>
        <name xml:lang="fr">Dépôt principal de mise à jour</name>
        <name xml:lang="gl">Repositorio de actualizacións principal</name>
        <name xml:lang="hr">Glavni repozitorij za dogradnju</name>
        <name xml:lang="hu">Elsődleges frissítéseket tartalmazó telepítési forrás</name>
        <name xml:lang="id">Repositori Pembaruan Utama</name>
        <name xml:lang="it">Repository principale degli aggiornamenti</name>
        <name xml:lang="ja">メインの更新用リポジトリ</name>
        <name xml:lang="km">ឃ្លាំង​ធ្វើ​បច្ចុប្បន្ន​​ចម្បង</name>
        <name xml:lang="ko">주 업데이트 저장소</name>
        <name xml:lang="lt">Pagrindinė atnaujinimų saugykla</name>
        <name xml:lang="nb">Hovedpakkebrønn for oppdateringer</name>
        <name xml:lang="nl">Hoofd-opslagruimte voor bijwerken</name>
        <name xml:lang="pa">ਮੇਨ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਰਿਪੋਜ਼ਟਰੀ</name>
        <name xml:lang="pl">Główne repozytorium aktualizacji</name>
        <name xml:lang="pt">Repositório Principal de Actualizações</name>
        <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Repositório principal de atualização</name>
        <name xml:lang="ro">Sursă principală de actualizări</name>
        <name xml:lang="ru">Основной репозиторий обновлений</name>
        <name xml:lang="sk">Hlavný repozitár s aktualizáciami</name>
        <name xml:lang="sv">Huvuduppderingsförråd</name>
        <name xml:lang="th">คลังแพกเกจหลักสำหรับปรับรุ่น</name>
        <name xml:lang="tr">Ana Güncelleme Deposu</name>
        <name xml:lang="uk">Головне сховище з оновленнями</name>
        <name xml:lang="wa">Mwaisse depot pol metaedje a djoû</name>
        <name xml:lang="zh_CN">主更新源</name>
        <name xml:lang="zh_TW">主要更新套件庫</name>
        <summary>Official update repository for Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ar">مستودع تحديث Tumbleweed الرئيسي</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ca">Repositori d'actualització oficial per al Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="cs">Oficiální aktualizační repozitář pro Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="da">Officiel opdateringskilde til Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="de">Offizielles Update-Repository für Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="el">Επίσημο αποθετήριο ενημερώσεων για Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="es">Repositorio oficial de actualizaciones para Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="et">Tumbleweedi ametlik uuenduste hoidla</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="fa">مخزن بروزرسانی رسمی برای Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="fi">Tumbleweedin virallinen päivityslähde</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="fr">Dépôt officiel de mise à jour pour Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="gl">Repositorio de actualización para Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="id">Repositori pembaruan resmi untuk Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="it">Repository degli aggiornamenti ufficiali per Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ja">Tumbleweed 向け公式更新リポジトリ</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="lt">Oficiali openSUSE Tumbleweed atnaujinimų saugykla</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="nb">Offisiel pakkebrønn for Tumbleweed oppdateringer</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="nl">Officiële opslagruimte voor bijwerken van Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="pl">Oficjalne repozytorium aktualizacji dla Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Repositório oficial de atualizações para o Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="ru">Официальный репозиторий обновлений для Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="sk">Oficiálny repozitár s aktualizáciami pre Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="sv">Förråd för officiella uppdateringar av Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="uk">Офіційне сховище оновлень для Tumbleweed</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">Tumbleweed 官方更新源</summary>
        <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">Tumbleweed 官方更新套件庫</summary>
        <description>This repository provides urgent updates until they get integrated into the main repositories.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ar">يوفر هذا المستودع تحديثات عاجلة حتى يتم دمجها في المستودعات الرئيسية.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ca">Aquest repositori proporciona actualitzacions urgents fins que s'integren als repositoris principals.</description>
        <description xml:lang="cs">Tento repozitář poskytuje akutní aktualizace, dokud nejsou zaintegrovány do hlavních repozitářů.</description>
        <description xml:lang="da">Denne softwarekilde leverer opdateringer som haster, indtil de bliver integreret i hovedsoftwarekilderne.</description>
        <description xml:lang="de">Diese Softwarequelle bietet wichtige Aktualisierungen bis diese in die Hauptrepositories integriert werden.</description>
        <description xml:lang="el">Αυτό το αποθετήριο παρέχει επείγοντες ενημερώσεις μέχρι να ενταχθούν στα κυρίως αποθετήρια.</description>
        <description xml:lang="es">Este repositorio provee actualizaciones urgentes hasta que sean integradas en los repositorios principales.</description>
        <description xml:lang="et">See hoidla pakub kiireid uuendusi, kuni nad on integreeritud peamistesse andmehoidlatesse.</description>
        <description xml:lang="fa">این مخزن بروزرسانی های فوری و ضروری را تا زمان یکپارچه شدن آنها درون مخازن اصلی برای شما مهیا میکند.</description>
        <description xml:lang="fi">Tämä asennuslähde tarjoaa kiireiset päivitykset ennen kuin ne saadaan viedyksi pääasennuslähteisiin.</description>
        <description xml:lang="fr">Ce dépôt fournit les mises à jour urgentes, avant qu'elles ne soient intégrées aux dépôts principaux.</description>
        <description xml:lang="gl">Este repositorio fornece actualizacións urxentes ata que sexan integradas nos repositorios principais.</description>
        <description xml:lang="id">Repositori ini menyediakan pembaruan penting sampai mereka terintegrasi ke dalam repositori utama.</description>
        <description xml:lang="it">Questo repository fornisce gli aggiornamenti urgenti fino a quando non vengono integrati nei repository principali.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ja">このリポジトリには、メインのリポジトリに統合されるよりも早く公開される、緊急の更新が含まれています。</description>
        <description xml:lang="lt">Šioje saugykloje pateikiami neatidėliotini atnaujinimai dar iki tol, kol jie patenka į pagrindines saugyklas.</description>
        <description xml:lang="nb">Denne pakkebrønnen tilbyr hasteoppdateringer inntil de blir integrert i hovedpakkebrønnene.</description>
        <description xml:lang="nl">Deze opslagruimte levert urgente elementen voor bijwerken totdat ze geïntegreerd worden in de hoofd-opslagruimten.</description>
        <description xml:lang="pl">To repozytorium dostarcza pilnych aktualizacji dopóki nie zostaną one dołączone do głównych repozytoriów.</description>
        <description xml:lang="pt_BR">Este repositório fornece atualizações urgentes até elas serem integradas nos repositórios oficiais.</description>
        <description xml:lang="ru">Этот репозиторий предоставляет срочные обновления до того, как они войдут в состав основных репозиториев.</description>
        <description xml:lang="sk">Tento repozitár poskytuje naliehavé aktualizácie, kým nie sú začlenené do hlavných repozitárov.</description>
        <description xml:lang="sv">Detta förråd tillhandahåller kritiska uppdateringar fram tills de blivit integrerade i huvudförrådet.</description>
        <description xml:lang="uk">Це сховище надає термінові оновлення до того, поки вони інтегруються в основні сховища.</description>
        <description xml:lang="zh_CN">此软件源提供了紧急更新，这些更新稍后会整合进主源。</description>
        <description xml:lang="zh_TW">這個套件庫提供急迫性高的更新，直到被整合進主要套件庫為止。</description>
        <url>http://download.opensuse.org/ports/ppc/update/tumbleweed/</url>
      </repository>
    </repositories>
  </group>
</metapackage>